I'm not buying it. How do you post childhood pics a few hours later, crisis actors pre-packaged
and ready to incite? So this is, um, a sister. I don't know what she's talking about. If she's
talking about Alex Preddy, um, that's an idiotic concept because people would post pictures of him
in his life, particularly to challenge the narrative that is being sent out about him as
some sort of terrorist. And what ends up happening is people who don't know better believe these lies.
And so you have to personalize people for folks. And the easiest way to do that is to show them as
children, as the innocent beings they were when they got here. Please just do your best to ignore
anyone who's in your comments, trying to gaslight you or trying to suggest that what you're seeing
is not what you're seeing. Whether that's about the individuals who are actively murdering people
in front of your face or the individuals who are actively truth telling and sharing the truth.
Like I had somebody yesterday be like, I've never seen a celebrity interact with a public like this.
What's your angle? You know what the angle is? You're a ridiculous person.
You're going to see people trying to discredit folks on this app who are trying to wake you up.
Listen to your intuition. This is why I keep trying to tell y'all, you have to establish a
relationship with your soul because they have got your mind. So you need to be establishing a
relationship with your soul and your spirit, your own relationship. You need to be listening to
yourself. You need to be outside, even if it's snowing, feeling the energy of the earth.
They've got your mind and the only way you're going to get it back is if you get your soul first
and it ain't going to be on this app. Support a real one.